Even if it's just for one day,
I will stay with her.
If you stay here,
you'll have less than a month left.
Sis,
do me a favor.
How do you want me to help you?
Be part of an act with me.
Hao Ruichi,
as long as there's still time,
I will spend every moment with her.
I want to help her do every little thing that brings happiness,
one by one.
To create an illusion where she's surrounded by happiness,
are you willing to trade your life?
Is it worth it?
Qi Miao lost her parents when she was very young.
They left her behind.
Since childhood,
she has only ever had one close friend.
At work,
she's always bullied.
In life,
she constantly encounters unlucky things.
She always looks strong on the surface,
but I know deep down,
what she fears most is abandonment.
That's why,
in this last month,
I want to spend it with her properly.
It's been a long time since we went out.
What are you writing?
A list of 100 little things couples do together.
Today,
is our first real date.
In the future,
there are thousands, even tens of thousands, of things
waiting for us to experience together.
But,
are you really feeling okay?
Shouldn't you rest for a few more days?
You don't trust me?
You—
What are you doing?
Alright, I get it, you're fine now.
Put me down.
No way.
I want to prove something.
In TV dramas, it's always the guy giving the girl a ride.
Why do you insist on giving me a ride?
That's just in TV dramas!
My boyfriend is a Star Messenger.
Of course, we have to be different from others.
Aren't you tired?
Not at all.
This is nothing.
Hold on tight.
I'm speeding up now.
Alright.
Here.
Eat slower this time.
Don't get yourself chilled again.
Am I as silly as you?
Hao Ruichi.
Thank you for coming to my side.
Thank you for becoming my lucky star.
Why are you saying this all of a sudden?
Because I feel so happy right now.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Oh, by the way...
That snail noodle we had last time was really good.
I want to eat it again.
Let’s go and have some.
Alright.
Wait for me a bit.
I'm heading to the restroom.
Okay.
Even if it's just a small amount of time,
I want to spend every moment with her,
doing everything that brings her happiness.
Every single thing.
To create an illusion of being surrounded by happiness for her,
would you trade your life?
Is it worth it?
Hao Ruichi,
you must be tired.
Why don’t we head home after dinner?
No way.
There are still so many things we haven’t done yet.
I've already felt so happy today.
Let's complete the items on our list,
one step at a time.
Excuse me,
sorry to bother you.
You two happen to be our 1,000th customers.
This meal is on the house!
However,
can we take a picture of you two to commemorate this?
Of course!
Boss,
there are so many people who come to eat here.
Do you really remember every one of them?
Of course I do.
Anyone who has been to our restaurant,
I remember them.
Every encounter is worth cherishing.
I just want to preserve more beautiful moments.
Let me take a photo of you two.
Come on.
Get a little closer, you two.
Ready? Here we go.
3, 2, 1... Cheese!
Perfect!
Let's do another pose,
one more photo.
3, 2, 1... Cheese!
I'll give you this photo as a keepsake.
You two make such a lovely couple.
Wishing you everlasting happiness.
We definitely will!
Thank you, boss!
You're not going home?
You just wanted to come here to keep an eye on me?
Let's just say,
we're getting a head start on living like an old married couple.
Hao Ruichi,
have you ever thought about
the kind of life you want in the future?
I want to wake up every day,
and see you by my side.
We’ll have a slow, peaceful breakfast together.
I'll get myself a job too.
Then,
I'll drive you to work in the morning,
and pick you up in the evening.
After dinner,
we can go for a stroll, just like today.
Let's talk about daily life.
During vacations,
we can go out and relax.
We can attend Alan's concert,
then catch up with Jian Dan and Ai Yi Te,
discussing life updates.
Of course,
sometimes we might argue.
I'll be the one to apologize first,
then cheer you up.
This,
this is the life I want.
Hao Ruichi,
let's go home.
Do you know
that I have my own idea of life too?
I want my life to be just like before.
I want Qi Dongdong causing trouble every day.
I want my life to remain chaotic as ever.
I want my parents to still be distant from me.
I want my misfortunes to continue to pile up.
Because,
because I want to trade all my good luck,
to trade for your good health,
to trade for your peace of mind for a lifetime.
I don't want to grow old so quickly.
I want,
I want us to be able to meet again someday.
To be able to sit here and chat together again,
to go for walks together,
to do a hundred little things together.